<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plugins on Crypta Tech</title>
    <link>localhost/plugins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plugins on Crypta Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="localhost/plugins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SeAT Fitting</title>
      <link>localhost/plugins/seat-fitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost/plugins/seat-fitting/</guid>
      <description>seat-fitting A module for SeAT that holds fittings and can compare the required skills for a fit to your character.


If you have issues with this, you can contact me on Eve as Denngarr B&amp;rsquo;tarn, or on email as &amp;lsquo;denngarr@cripplecreekcorp.com&amp;rsquo;
Quick Installation: In your seat directory (By default: /var/www/seat), type the following:
php artisan down composer require denngarr/seat-fitting php artisan vendor:publish --force --all php artisan migrate php artisan up And now, when you log into &amp;lsquo;Seat&amp;rsquo;, you should see a &amp;lsquo;Fittings&amp;rsquo; link on the left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeAT Squad Sync</title>
      <link>localhost/plugins/seat-squad-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost/plugins/seat-squad-sync/</guid>
      <description>A module for SeAT that allows for creating a link between the members of a


Usage This plugin provides a very simple yet powerful functionality that allows syncing squad members to role affiliations.
This allows for squads to be created which act as for example a recruitment squad. People who want to apply to corp join the squad. This plugin will then sync the character to be a part of the affiliations of the linked recruitment role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SeAT SRP</title>
      <link>localhost/plugins/seat-srp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost/plugins/seat-srp/</guid>
      <description>A module for SeAT that tracks SRP requests
This plugin write for SeAT is providing to your instance a way to manage your ship replacement program (SRP)
  
If you have issues with this, you can contact me on Eve as Crypta Electrica, or on email as &amp;lsquo;crypta@crypta.tech&amp;rsquo;
Quick Installation: In your seat directory (By default: /var/www/seat), type the following:
php artisan down composer require denngarr/seat-srp (You can skip this step if you are running 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seat Text</title>
      <link>localhost/plugins/seat-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost/plugins/seat-text/</guid>
      <description>A module for SeAT that allows for creating plaintext shareable pages


Usage Quick Installation Docker Install Open the .env file (which is most probably at /opt/seat-docker/.env) and edit the SEAT_PLUGINS variable to include the package.
# SeAT Plugins # This is a list of the all of the third party plugins that you # would like to install as part of SeAT. Package names should be # comma separated if multiple packages should be installed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
